MAYUR KHANDARE

SALESFORCE DEVELOPER

+91-8830841424



<u>mayurkhandare97@gmail.com</u>



https://trailblazer.me/id/mayurkhandare

Personal LWC Projects



https://mkportfolio-dev-ed.my.site.com/

SKILLS

- Lightning Web Components
- Apex Classes, Apex Triggers
- Asynchronous Apex (Batch Apex, Schedulable Classes, Future Methods)
- SOQL and SOSL
- Process Automation Tools (Flow Builder, Process Builder, Workflow rules)
- Apex Integration
- Salesforce Administration

ACHIEVEMENTS

- INSTA AWARD FY22-Q4
- SUPERBADGES

Apex Specialist

Process Automation Specialist

CERTIFICATIONS

- Infosys Certified Salesforce Developer
- Infosys Certified Salesforce Administrator
- Salesforce Developer Virtual Internship Issued On: July 02, 2022

Verify at: http://surl.li/eedle

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Engineering from Pune University (2016-2020)

Sinhgad Academy of Engineering, Kondhwa BK

7.86 CGPA (First Class with Distinction)

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional salesforce developer with 2.3+years of experience. Looking for a challenging career and be a part of progressive organization that gives a scope to enhance my knowledge and utilizing my skills towards the growth of the organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INFOSYS LIMITED

Senior Systems Engineer Systems Engineer

Oct 2022 -Present Jan 2021 - Sept 2022

- Experience on working on Apex classes, Triggers, Batch Apex, Test Classes, SOQL queries, Collections.
- Good exposure in salesforce customization and relationships.
- Experience in automation process with approval process, process builder, workflow rules and flow builder.
- Experience on working on Lightning Web Components.
- Good Exposure on Apex Integration.
- Experience in developing Custom Objects, Custom Fields, Page Layouts, Tabs, Record Type, Field Dependencies, Relationships, Validation Rules.

PROJECTS

Domain - Banking & Finance Product - CRM Sales Cloud

Role and Responsibilities:

- I have worked as a Salesforce Developer where I contributed to do technical transformation of the bank's CRM solution across processes within Loan approval and Credit Card line of business.
- We worked on agile process, dealing with series of sprints, daily status calls, sprint planning sessions etc.
- Worked with Apex classes, Apex triggers, SOQL and SOSL.
- Developed Lightning Web Components to build business functionality.
- Developed Batch classes to implement bulk record functionality.
- Designed Custom Objects, Custom Tabs, Validation Rules, Workflow Rules, Page layouts, Approval Process to suit to the needs of the application.
- Effectively Used Data Migration tools like Apex Data Loader and Import Wizard.
- Developed Flows to build case journeys, update fields, call sub flows and fire real time SMS/ emails.